<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<executable>
  <category>Chest Imaging Platform.Toolkit.Processing</category>
  <title>GenerateAtlasConvexHull</title>
  <description><![CDATA[his program reads atlas lung images and generates a convex hull image \
  corresponding to them. It is assumed that the atlas exists as two separate atlases: one for \
  the left lung and one for the right. It is also assumed that the the maximum value in each \
  corresponds to a probability of 1 and the value 0 corresponds to a probability of 0. The \
  algorithm proceeds by reading in the left atlas and thresholding according to a specified \
  probability threhold (a float-valued quantity ranging from 0 to 1). The right atlas is read \
  in and similarly thresholded. The union of the two images is created, and the resulting \
  image is downsampled for faster processing. After downsampling, the convex hull is created. \
  The convex hull is represented as a binary image (0 = background, 1 = foreground). The \
  convex hull is upsampled so that it has the same extent as the original image, and it is \
  then written to file.]]></description>
  <version>0.0.1</version>
  <documentation-url>https://chestimagingplatform.org/processing</documentation-url>
  <license>Slicer</license>
  <contributor> Applied Chest Imaging Laboratory, Brigham and Women's hospital</contributor>
  <acknowledgements>This work is funded by the National Heart, Lung, And Blood Institute of the National \
        Institutes of Health under Award Number R01HL116931. The content is solely the responsibility of the authors \
        and does not necessarily represent the official views of the National Institutes of Health.
    </acknowledgements>

  <parameters>
    <image>
      <name>leftAtlasFileName</name>
      <label>Left Atlas Filename</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>l</flag>
      <longflag>--leftAtlas</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Left lung atlas file name]]></description>
      <default>q</default>
    </image>
    <image>
      <name>rightAtlasFileName</name>
      <label>right Atlas FileName</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>r</flag>
      <longflag>--rightAtlas</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Right lung atlas file name]]></description>
      <default>q</default>
    </image>
    <geometry>
      <name>outputFileName</name>
      <label>output Filename</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>o</flag>
      <longflag>--output</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Output convex hull file name]]></description>
      <default>q</default>
    </geometry>
    <integer>
      <name>numRotations</name>
      <label>number of Rotations</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>n</flag>
      <longflag>--numRotations</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Number of rotations. This quanity relates to the accuracy of the final \
      convex hull. Increasing the number of rotations increases accuracy. If this quantity changes, \
      so should the resolution degrees parameter (specified by the -dr flag). E.g. if number of \
      rotations increases by a factor of two, degrees resolution should decrease by a factor \
      of two.]]></description>
      <default>1</default>
    </integer>   


    <float>
      <name>degreesResolution</name>
      <label>degrees of Resolution</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>d</flag>
      <longflag>--degrees</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Degrees resolution. This quanity relates to the accuracy of the \
      final convex hull. Decreasing the degrees resolution increases accuracy. If this quantity \
      changes, so should the number of rotations parameter (specified by the -nr flag). E.g. if \
      number of rotations increases by a factor of two, degrees resolution should decrease by \
      a factor of two]]></description>
      <default>45</default>
    </float>  
    <float>
      <name>downsampleFactor</name>
      <label>downsample Factor</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>s</flag>
      <longflag>--sample</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Down sample factor]]></description>
      <default>1</default>
    </float>  
    <float>
      <name>probabilityThreshold</name>
      <label>probability Threshold</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>p</flag>
      <longflag>--probability</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Probability threshold in the interval [0,1]. This parameter \
      controls the level at which the atlas is thresholded prior to convex hull \
      creation]]></description>
      <default>0.5</default>
    </float>  
  </parameters>
</executable>
