<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<executable>
    <category>Chest Imaging Platform.Toolkit.Particles</category>
    <title>FilterAirwayParticleData</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This program reads airway particles and filters them \
based on connected components analysis. Particles are placed in \
the same component provided they are sufficiently close to one \
another, have scale that is sufficiently similar, and sufficiently \
define a local cylinder (i.e. they are sufficiently parallel with the \
vector connecting the two paticle spatial locations). Only \
components that have cardinality greater than or equal to that \
specified by the user will be retained in the output. Furthermore, \
the output particles will have a defined 'unmergedComponents' \
array that indicates the component label assigned to each particle.]]>
    </description>
    <version>0.0.1</version>
    <documentation-url>https://chestimagingplatform.org/particles</documentation-url>
    <license>Slicer</license>
    <contributor> Applied Chest Imaging Laboratory, Brigham and Women's Hospital</contributor>
    <acknowledgements>This work is funded by the National Heart, Lung, And Blood Institute of the National \
Institutes of Health under Award Number R01HL116931. The content is solely the responsibility of the authors \
and does not necessarily represent the official views of the National Institutes of Health.
    </acknowledgements>
    
    <parameters>
      <label>IO</label>
        <description>Input/output parameters</description>
        <geometry type="model">
            <name>inParticlesFileName</name>
            <label>Input Particles FileName</label>
            <channel>input</channel>
            <flag>i</flag>
            <longflag>iap</longflag>
            <description><![CDATA[Input particles file name]]></description>
            <default>NA</default>
        </geometry>
      
        <geometry type="model">
          <name>outParticlesFileName</name>
          <label>Output Particles File Name</label>
          <channel>output</channel>
          <flag>o</flag>
          <longflag>oap</longflag>
          <description><![CDATA[Output particles file name]]></description>
          <default>NA</default>
        </geometry>
      </parameters>
  
    <parameters>
      <label>Parameters</label>      
        <double>
            <name>maxAllowableDistance</name>
            <label>Maximum Allowable Distance</label>
            <flag>d</flag>
            <longflag>dist</longflag>
            <channel>input</channel>
            <description>Maximum inter-particle distance. Two particles must be at least this close \
together to be considered for connectivity. 
	    </description>
            <default>3.0</default>
        </double>

        <double>
            <name>particleAngleThreshold</name>
            <label>Particle Angle Threshold</label>
            <flag>a</flag>
            <longflag>angle</longflag>
            <channel>input</channel>
            <description>Particle angle threshold used to test the connectivity between two particles (in degrees). \
The vector connecting two particles is computed. The angle formed between the connecting vector and the particle Hessian \
eigenvector pointing in the direction of the airway axis is then considered. For both particles, this angle must be below \
the specified threshold for the particles to be connected.</description>
            <default>20.0</default>
        </double>
        
        <double>
            <name>scaleRatioThreshold</name>
            <label>Scale Ratio Threshold</label>
            <flag>r</flag>
            <longflag>ratio</longflag>
            <channel>input</channel>
            <description>Scale ratio threshold in the interval [0,1]. This value indicates the degree to which \
two particles can differ in scale and still be considered for connectivity. The higher the value, the more permisse the filter is \
with respect to scale differences.</description>
            <default>1.0</default>
        </double>
        
        <integer>
            <name>maxComponentSizeTemp</name>
            <label>Maximum Component Size</label>
            <longflag>maxSize</longflag>
            <flag>m</flag>
            <channel>input</channel>
            <description>Maximum component size. No component will be larger than the specified size </description>
            <default>10000</default>
        </integer>
        
        <integer>
            <name>componentSizeThresholdTemp</name>
            <label>Component Size Threshold</label>
            <longflag>size</longflag>
            <flag>s</flag>
            <channel>input</channel>
            <description>Component size cardinality threshold. Only components with this many particles or more \
will be retained in the output. </description>
            <default>0</default>
        </integer>
      
        <double>
          <name>maxAllowableScale</name>
          <longflag>maxScale</longflag>
          <description>Max allowable scale. No connection will be made between two particles if either of them \
have a scale that exceeds this amount.</description>
          <label>Maximum allowable scale</label>
          <default>100</default>
        </double>
        
        <double>
          <name>minAllowableScale</name>
          <longflag>minScale</longflag>
          <description>Min allowable scale. No connection will be made between two particles if either of them \
have a scale that exceeds this amount.</description>
          <label>Minimum allowable scale</label>
          <default>0</default>
        </double>
      
    </parameters>
</executable>
