<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<executable>
  <category>Chest Imaging Platform.Toolkit.Utils</category>
  <title>MergeChestLabelMaps</title>
  <description><![CDATA[This program will merge an overlay label map into a base label map. \
  The user must indicate which structures should be merged. Structures can be chest regions, \
  chest types, and or region-type pairs. Only the structures specified will be merged from the \
  overlay label map onto the base label map.]]>
  </description>
  <version>0.0.1</version>
  <documentation-url>https://chestimagingplatform.org/utils</documentation-url>
  <license>Slicer</license>
  <contributor> Applied Chest Imaging Laboratory, Brigham and Women's hospital</contributor>
  <acknowledgements>This work is funded by the National Heart, Lung, And Blood Institute of the National \
    Institutes of Health under Award Number R01HL116931. The content is solely the responsibility of the authors \
    and does not necessarily represent the official views of the National Institutes of Health.
  </acknowledgements>

  <parameters>
    <label>IO</label>
    <description>Input/output parameters</description>
    <image>
      <name>baseLabelMapFileName</name>
      <label>Base label map</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>b</flag>
      <longflag>base</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[All labels in the base image remain untouched except for the rules specified by the user applied \
      to the information in the overlay label map.]]></description>
    </image>  

    <image>
      <name>overlayLabelMapFileName</name>
      <label>Overlay label map</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>overlay</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Contains labels that will be used together with the specified rules to update the base label map.]]></description>
    </image>  

    <image>
      <name>outLabelMapFileName</name>
      <label>Output label map</label>
      <channel>output</channel>
      <flag>o</flag>
      <longflag>out</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Output label map]]></description>
    </image>  
  </parameters>

  <parameters>
    <label>Rules</label>
    <description> Rules to apply in the merge process</description>
    <boolean>
      <name>applyUnion</name>
      <label>Apply union</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>union</longflag>
      <flag>u</flag>
      <description>Setting Union to be true results in the following behavior: for a given \
      voxel, if either the region or type is undefined for either of the base \
      or overlay label maps, then the merged voxel will get the defined \
      region/type. If there is a conflict in defined regions for a given voxel, \
      if one region is a subset of the other region, then the merged voxel \
      will get the region that is more specific. Otherwise, if there is a \
      region/type conflict that can't be resolved, then the region/type in \
      the base image is used. This option is false by default, and if set to \
      true, will trump all other rules. </description>
    </boolean>

    <string-vector>
      <name>overrideTypes</name>
      <label>Override chest types</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>otypes</longflag>
      <description>Any voxel in the base (input) image with this type will be set to UNDEFINEDTYPE first, and then \
      the type specified will be set according to the locations of that type in the overlay image</description>
    </string-vector>

    <string-vector>
      <name>overrideRegions</name>
      <label>Override chest regions</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>oregions</longflag>
      <description>Any voxel in the base (input) image with this region will be set to UNDEFINEDREGION first, and then \
      the region specified will be set according to the locations of that region in the overlay image</description>
    </string-vector>

    <string-vector>
      <name>overrideRegionTypePairs</name>
      <label>Override chest region, chest type pairs</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>opairs</longflag>
      <description>Any voxel in the base (input) image with this region-type pair combination will have \
      the type set to UNDEFINEDTYPE. The region will be untouched. All voxels in the overlay image having \
      the specifed pair will have their type grafted onto the base image. The list of comma separated string \
      values passed with this flag will be interpreted as a list of pairs, where the first member of the pair \
      will be interpreted as the region value, and the second element of the pair will be considered as the type.</description>
    </string-vector>

    <string-vector>
      <name>mergeTypes</name>
      <label>Merge chest types</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>mtypes</longflag>
      <description>The type specified will be set according to the locations of that type in the overlay image </description>
    </string-vector>

    <string-vector>
      <name>mergeRegions</name>
      <label>Merge chest regions</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>mregions</longflag>
      <description>The region specified will be set according to the locations of that region in the overlay image</description>
    </string-vector>

    <string-vector>
      <name>mergeRegionTypePairs</name>
      <label>Merge chest region, chest type pairs</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>mpairs</longflag>
      <description>All voxels having the specified region-type in the overlay image will be merged with the base image -- only the type will be \
      grafted onto the base image, however. The specified region serves to identify the voxels in the overlay image, but the value of the \
      region itself is not grafted</description>
    </string-vector>
  </parameters>

</executable>
