<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<executable>
  <category>Chest Imaging Platform.Toolkit.Processing</category>
  <title>GenerateLobeSurfaceModels</title>
  <description><![CDATA[This program is used to generate fissure shape models based \
on a training set. The basic approach is as follows: a reference image \
is read and then registered to the label map for which the user \
wants to produce fissure models. Additionally, a set of training \
data is read in. These data sets consist of fissure indices and a \
transform file that indicates the mapping between the training data \
label map and the reference label map. Once the reference image is \
registered to the input image, the resulting transform in \
conjunction with the training data transform is used to map the \
training fissure points to the input image's coordinate frame. This \
is done repeatedly for all the training data sets. Once all the \
fissure points are in the coordinate frame of the input image, PCA \
is performed to get the mean and modes of the fissure points. This \
data is then printed to file. \
\
The output file format is as follows: the first line contains the \
origin of the input image. The second line contains the spacing of \
the input image. The third line indicates the number of modes, \
N. The fourth line is the mean vector. The entries are for the \
continuous index z-values of the control points. The next N lines \
contain the mode variances and a weight value. Upon generation of \
the shape model file, the weight value will be 0. Later in the lobe \
segmentation process, this value can be overwritten with a weight \
has been found by fitting to particles data. The next N lines are \
the modes themselves -- again, the modes represent the variation of \
the control points in the z-direction (the range of our TPS \
function). The length of each mode (and mean) vector is m, where m \
indicates the number of control points. Finally, the next m lines \
indicate the control point indices (the domain locations). Note \
that the z-value for these entries is 0. This is to emphasize that \
they are in the domain -- the x-y plane. Two shape model files can \
be saved: one for the left lung and one for the right lung. In the \
right lung PCA is performed over the right oblique and right horizontal \
surfaces taken together. In the corresponding saved file, the first \
half of the points represent the right oblique surface, and the \
second half of the points represent the right horizontal surface. \
Note that the right oblique and right horizontal surfaces share the \
same points in the domain.]]>
  </description>
  <version>0.0.1</version>
  <documentation-url>https://chestimagingplatform.org/processing</documentation-url>
  <license>Slicer</license>
  <contributor> Applied Chest Imaging Laboratory, Brigham and Women's hospital</contributor>
  <acknowledgements>This work is funded by the National Heart, Lung, And Blood Institute of the National \
Institutes of Health under Award Number R01HL116931. The content is solely the responsibility of the authors \
and does not necessarily represent the official views of the National Institutes of Health.
  </acknowledgements>

  <parameters>
    <label>IO</label>
    <description>Input/output parameters</description>

    <image>
      <name>inputFileName</name>
      <label>Input label map</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>ilm</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Input label map to serve as starting point for lung lobe \
segmentation .The level of lung segmentation 'grunularity' should be at the left lung right lung split \
level. In other words, a mask divided into thirds (left and right) will work fine, as will one for which \
only the left and right lung are labeled]]></description>
    </image>  

    <image>
      <name>refImageFileName</name>
      <label>Reference label map</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>irlm</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Reference image label map corresponding to the reference points. \
This is the image to which all other image data in the training set is registered to.]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </image>  

    <string>
      <name>resourcesDir</name>
      <label>Resources Directory</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>dir</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Directory containing resources needed to build the shape model. \
This directory is expected to contain a collection of file pairs: a transform file and a \
region and type points file. Each pair corresponds to a single case. The transform file \
indicates how to transform the case so that it aligns with a reference case and is expected \
to have the extension '_TO_10002K_INSP_STD_BWH_COPD_transform.txt'. The region and type \
points file contains physical coordinates along the right horizontal, right oblique, and left oblique \
lobe boundaries. It is expected to have the extension '_regionAndTypePoints.csv'. For a given pair \
the prefix is expected to be the same.]]>
      </description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </string>  

    <file fileExtensions=".csv">
      <name>rightShapeModelFileName</name>
      <label>Right oblique and right horizontal shape model file name</label>
      <channel>output</channel>
      <longflag>orsm</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Output right oblique and right horizontal shape model file name. The first \
half of the entries in the saved fill will correspond to the right oblique boundary surface. \
The second half of the entries will correspond to the right horizontal boundary surface.]]>
      </description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </file>  

    <file fileExtensions=".csv">
      <name>leftShapeModelFileName</name>
      <label>Left shape model file name</label>
      <channel>output</channel>
      <longflag>olsm</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Output left lung shape model file name. This file will contain the shape model \
describing the boundary between the left upper and left lower lobes.]]>
      </description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </file>  

    <string>
      <name>outRefToInputTransformFileName</name>
      <label>Output Transform File Name</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>ot</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Output reference image to input label map transform file name.]]>
      </description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </string>  
  </parameters>

  <parameters>
    <double>
      <name>maxStepLength</name>
      <longflag>max</longflag>
      <description>Maximum step length for registration</description>
      <label>Max step length</label>
      <default>1.0</default>
    </double>

    <double>
      <name>minStepLength</name>
      <longflag>min</longflag>
      <description>Minimum step length for registration</description>
      <label>Min Step Length</label>
      <default>0.001</default>
    </double>

    <double>
      <name>translationScale</name>
      <flag>t</flag>
      <longflag>transScale</longflag>
      <description>Translation scale for affine registration</description>
      <label>Translation scale</label>
      <default>0.001</default>
    </double>

    <double>
      <name>downsampleFactor</name>
      <flag>d</flag>
      <longflag>down</longflag>
      <description>Downsample factor to apply before registration
      </description>
      <label>Downsample Factor</label>
      <default>4.0</default>
    </double>

    <integer>
      <name>numberOfIterations</name>
      <flag>n</flag>
      <longflag>numIters</longflag>
      <description>Number of iterations</description>
      <label>Number of iterations</label>
      <default>20</default>
    </integer>

  </parameters>
</executable>
