<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<executable>
  <category>Chest Imaging Platform</category>
  <title>ExtractChestLabelMap</title>
  <description><![CDATA[This program takes in a lung label map and producs a lung \
  label map; it assumes the labeling conventions coded in cipConventions.h. \
  The user specifies the regions and types he/she is \
  interested in.  All other regions/types are set to UNDEFINEDTYPE \
  and UNDEFINEDREGION.  Given that regions are hierarchical, a region \
  that is higher in the hierarchy will be preferred to one that is \
  lower.  E.g., if the user specifies both WHOLELUNG and \
  LEFTSUPERIORLOBE, the region in the LEFTSUPERIORLOBE will be defined as \
  such, and WHOLELUNG will be used elsewhere. Precedence will be as \
  follows: types, regions, region-type pairs. In \
  other words, if the user requests both LEFTLUNG and AIRWAY (not as a \
  pair), then an AIRWAY voxel in the LEFTLUNG will be mapped to LEFTLUNG \
  in the output. If the user additionally requests the AIRWAY, LEFTLUNG \
  pair, then the entire voxel will be preserved.]]></description>
  <version>0.0.1</version>
  <license>Slicer</license>
  <contributor> Applied Chest Imaging Laboratory, Brigham and women's hospital</contributor>
  <acknowledgements>This work is funded by the National Heart, Lung, And Blood Institute of the National \
        Institutes of Health under Award Number R01HL116931. The content is solely the responsibility of the authors \
        and does not necessarily represent the official views of the National Institutes of Health.</acknowledgements>
  <parameters>
    <string-vector>
      <name>regionVec</name>
      <label>Chest Regions</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>r</flag>
      <longflag>--regions</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Specify a chest you want to extract]]></description>
    </string-vector>  

    <string-vector>
      <name>typeVec</name>
      <label>Chest Types</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>t</flag>
      <longflag>--types</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Specify a chest type you want to extract]]></description>
    </string-vector>  

    <string-vector>
      <name>regionPairVec</name>
      <label>Chest Region-Type Pair Region</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>--regionPair</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Specify a region in a region-type pair you want to extract]]></description>
    </string-vector>  

    <string-vector>
      <name>typePairVec</name>
      <label>Chest Region-Type Pair Type</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>--typePair</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Specify a type in a region-type pair you want to extract]]></description>
    </string-vector>  
  </parameters>

  <parameters>
    <label>IO</label>
    <description>Input/output parameters</description>
    <image>
      <name>inFileName</name>
      <label>Input label map file name</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>i</flag>
      <longflag>--inFileName</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Input label map file name]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </image>  

    <image>
      <name>outFileName</name>
      <label>Output label map file name</label>
      <channel>output</channel>
      <flag>o</flag>
      <longflag>--outFileName</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Output label map file name]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </image>  
  </parameters>

</executable>