<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<executable>
    <category>Chest Imaging Platform.Toolkit.Utils</category>
    <title>ReadNRRDsWriteVTK</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This program reads a number of NRRD files and collects the data in those files into \
a single VTK polydata file for writing. The input data files typically contain particles information.]]>
    </description>
    <version>0.0.1</version>
    <documentation-url>https://chestimagingplatform.org/utils</documentation-url>
    <license>Slicer</license>
    <contributor> Applied Chest Imaging Laboratory, Brigham and Women's Hospital</contributor>
    <acknowledgements>This work is funded by the National Heart, Lung, And Blood Institute of the National \
        Institutes of Health under Award Number R01HL116931. The content is solely the responsibility of the authors \
        and does not necessarily represent the official views of the National Institutes of Health.
    </acknowledgements>
    
    <parameters>
        <label>IO</label>
        <description>Input/output parameters</description>
        <file multiple="true">
            <name>inFileNameVecArg</name>
            <label>Input FileName Vector</label>
            <channel>input</channel>
            <flag>i</flag>
            <longflag>inFileName</longflag>
            <description><![CDATA[Specify an input NRRD file name followed by a string (using the -a or --arrayName flags) \
                designating the name of the array in the output vtk file. Can specify multiple inputs. Note that a file name specified \
                with this flag must immediately be followed by a corresponding array name using the -a or --arrayName flags. \
                Files that are 1xN are assumed to have scalar data, 3xN are assumed to have vector data, and 9xN are assumed to \
                have matrix data. A 4xN file is assumed to contain spatial coordinates for the first 3 components and a scale \
                component for the 4th. Note that in this case, the string value assigned to this file is just a placeholder -- \
                the scale data will be placed in matrix with name 'scale'. 7xN files are assumed to have the following format: \
                mask xx xy xz yy yz zz, so a matrix is constructed using the components in the following order: [1 2 3 2 4 5 3 5 6] \
                (zero-based indexing).]]></description>
            <default>NA</default>
        </file>
        
        <string multiple="true">
            <name>arrayNameVecArg</name>
            <label>Array Name Vec</label>
            <channel>input</channel>
            <flag>a</flag>
            <longflag>arrayName</longflag>
            <description><![CDATA[Array names corresponding to files immediately preceding invocation of this flag (specified \
with the -i or --inFileName flags). Array names follow conventinos laid out in the ACIL wiki for particles polydata point \
data arrays]]></description>
            <default>NA</default>
        </string>
        
        
         <string>
            <name>outFileName</name>
            <label>Output File Name</label>
            <channel>output</channel>
            <flag>o</flag>
            <longflag>outFileName</longflag>
            <description><![CDATA[Ouput vtk file name. All particles information will be stored in this file.]]></description>
            <default>NA</default>
        </string>
         
        <float>
           <name>irad</name>
           <label>interparticle Radius</label>
           <longflag>irad</longflag>
           <description><![CDATA[Store interparticle radius. This metadata information is stored as field data in an array name "irad".]]></description>
           <default>0</default>
        </float>
        
        <float>
          <name>srad</name>
          <label>scale Radius</label>
          <longflag>srad</longflag>
          <description><![CDATA[Store scale radius. This metadata information is stored as field data in an array name "srad".]]></description>
          <default>0</default>
        </float>
          
        <float-vector>
          <name>spacing</name>
          <label>Spacing</label>
          <longflag>spacing</longflag>
          <description><![CDATA[Spacing of the volume data that generated the particles. This metadata info is stored as a field data in an array named "spacing"]]></description>
            <default>0,0,0</default>
        </float-vector>
 
        <float>
          <name>liveThreshold</name>
          <label>Live Threshold</label>
          <longflag>liveth</longflag>
          <description><![CDATA[Live threshold parameter that generated the particle's result. This metadata info is stored as a field data in an array named "liveth"]]></description>
            <default>0</default>
        </float>
          
        <float>
            <name>seedThreshold</name>
            <label>Seed Threshold</label>
            <longflag>seedth</longflag>
            <description><![CDATA[Seed treshold parameter that generated the particle's result. This metadata info is stored as a field data in an array named "seedth"]]></description>
              <default>0</default>
        </float>

        <boolean>
          <name>binaryOutput</name>
          <label>VTK binary output file</label>
          <flag>b</flag>
          <longflag>binary</longflag>
          <description><![CDATA[Ouput vtk file name in binary format.]]></description>
          <default>false</default>
        </boolean>
        
        <string>
          <name>cipRegionArg</name>
          <label>Chest Region</label>
          <channel>input</channel>
          <longflag>cipr</longflag>
          <description><![CDATA[Chest region for particles labeling. UndefinedRegion by default]]></description>
          <default>UndefinedRegion</default>
       </string>

       <string>
         <name>cipTypeArg</name>
         <label>Chest Type</label>
         <channel>input</channel>
         <longflag>cipt</longflag>
         <description><![CDATA[Chest type for particles labeling. UndefinedType by default]]></description>
         <default>UndefinedType</default>
      </string>

    </parameters>
</executable>
