<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<executable>
  <category>Chest Imaging Platform.Toolkit.Processing</category>
  <title>GenerateStatisticsForAirwayGenerationLabeling</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This program computes statistics needed as inputs to the LabelAirwayParticlesByGeneration program. It computes these statistics over (possibly) multiple, labeled input airway particles datasets. The user must specify information needed to construct the minimum spanning tree (which encodes topology over the particles). This information should be the same that is used for the LabelAirwayParticlesByGeneration program.]]>
    </description>
  <version>0.0.1</version>
  <documentation-url>https://chestimagingplatform.org/processing</documentation-url>
  <license>Slicer</license>
  <contributor> Applied Chest Imaging Laboratory, Brigham and Women's Hospital</contributor>
  <acknowledgements>This work is funded by the National Heart, Lung, And Blood Institute of the National Institutes of Health \
    under Award Number R01HL116931. The content is solely the responsibility of the authors \
    and does not necessarily represent the official views of the National Institutes of Health.
  </acknowledgements>

  <parameters>
  <label>I/O</label>
  <description>Input/Output</description>
      <string-vector>
          <name>inParticlesFileNamesArg</name>
          <longflag>input</longflag>
          <flag>i</flag>
          <label>Input particles file names</label>
          <channel>input</channel>
          <description><![CDATA[Input particles file names.]]>
          </description>
      </string-vector>
      <geometry type="model">
          <name>refParticlesFileName</name>
          <label>ref Particles FileName</label>
          <channel>input</channel>
          <flag>r</flag>
          <longflag>ref</longflag>
          <description><![CDATA[Specify a (labeled) reference particle dataset to compute statistics for emission probabilities. For each particle in this dataset, every other particle in the files specified with the -i flag will be considered. If the two particles have the same generation label and are within the distance specified by the --ed flag, then the scale difference, angle, and distance between the particles will be computed and used to compute the class conditional probabilities for that generation. This is an optional argument. Note that if it is specified, the same file should not also appear as an input specified with the -i flag.]]></description>
          <default>q</default>
      </geometry>
      <file fileExtensions=".csv">
          <name>emissionProbsFileName</name>
          <label>emission Probs FileName</label>
          <channel>output</channel>
          <flag>e</flag>
          <description><![CDATA[csv file in which to write the computed emission probability statistics.]]></description>
          <default>q</default>
      </file>
      
      <file fileExtensions=".csv">
          <name>normTransProbsMeanVarFileName</name>
          <label>norm Trans Probs Mean Var FileName</label>
          <channel>output</channel>
          <longflag>ntp</longflag>
          <description><![CDATA[csv file in which to write the computed transition probability scale and angle statics.]]></description>
          <default>q</default>
      </file>
      
      <file fileExtensions=".csv">
          <name>transProbsFileName</name>
          <label>Trans Probs FileName</label>
          <channel>output</channel>
          <longflag>tp</longflag>
          <description><![CDATA[csv file in which to write the transition probabilities. The output will be an 11x11 matrix. The rows indicate the 'from' generation and the columns represent the 'to' generation. The probabilities are computed simply by counting the number of times a given transition occurs and then normalizing.]]></description>
          <default>q</default>
      </file>
    </parameters>

    <parameters>
    <label>Parameters</label>
    <description>Parameters</description>
    <double>
      <name>particleDistanceThreshold</name>
      <label>Particle Distance Threshold</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>d</flag>
      <longflag>distThresh</longflag>
        <description><![CDATA[Particle distance threshold for constructing minimum spanning tree. Particles further apart than this distance will not have an edge placed between them in the weighted graph passed to the min spanning tree algorithm]]></description>
      <default>20.0</default>
    </double>
    <double>
        <name>emissionProbDistThresh</name>
        <label>emission Prob Distance Threshold</label>
        <channel>input</channel>
        <longflag>ed</longflag>
        <description><![CDATA[The radius of the epsilon ball used when considering if a particle should be considered for computing the class-conditional emission probabilities. Only necessary if a reference particle dataset is specified with the --ed flag.]]></description>
        <default>20.0</default>   
    </double>
        
  </parameters>
</executable>
