<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<executable>
  <category>Chest Imaging Platform.Toolkit.Processing</category>
  <title>GenerateDistanceMapFromLabelMap</title>
<description><![CDATA[This program can be used to compute a distance map from an \
input label map (that adheres to the CIP label map conventions \
laid out in cipConventions.h). The user must specify which \
structure of interest the distance map should be computed with \
respect to by indicating the chest region and/or chest type. If \
the chest type is not specified, any voxel meeting the indicated \
chest type will be set to foreground and vice versa. The user also \
has the option of downsampling the label map prior to distance map \
computation, which should speed computation time. The resulting \
distance map will by upsampled by the same amount before writing.]]></description>
  <version>0.0.1</version>
  <documentation-url>https://chestimagingplatform.org/processing</documentation-url>
  <license>Slicer</license>
  <contributor> Applied Chest Imaging Laboratory, Brigham and Women's hospital</contributor>
  <acknowledgements>This work is funded by the National Heart, Lung, And Blood Institute of the National \
        Institutes of Health under Award Number R01HL116931. The content is solely the responsibility of the authors \
        and does not necessarily represent the official views of the National Institutes of Health.</acknowledgements>

  <parameters>

    <string>
      <name>labelMapFileName</name>
      <label>Label Map File Name</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>l</flag>
      <longflag>labelMap</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Input label map file name]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </string>

    <string>
      <name>distanceMapFileName</name>
      <label>Distance Map File Name</label>
      <flag>d</flag>
      <longflag>distanceMap</longflag>
      <channel>output</channel>
      <description><![CDATA[Output distance map file name]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </string>
    
    <double>
        <name>downsampleFactor</name>
        <label>Downsample Factor</label>
        <flag>s</flag>
        <longflag>downsample</longflag>
        <channel>input</channel>
        <description><![CDATA[Downsample factor. The input label map will be \
            downsampled by the specified amount before the distance map is computed. The resulting \
            distance map will then be scaled up by the same amount before writing.]]></description>
        <default>1.0</default>
    </double>
      
      <integer>
          <name>cipRegionTemp</name>
          <label>cip Region</label>
          <flag>r</flag>
          <longflag>region</longflag>
          <channel>input</channel>
          <description><![CDATA[Specify the chest region of the object the distance \
              map is to be computed with respect to. UNDEFINEDREGION by default]]></description>
          <default>0</default>
      </integer>  
      
      <integer>
          <name>cipTypeTemp</name>
          <label>cip Type</label>
          <flag>t</flag>
          <longflag>type</longflag>
          <channel>input</channel>
          <description><![CDATA[Specify the chest type of the object the distance \
              map is to be computed with respect to. UNDEFINEDTYPE by default]]></description>
          <default>0</default>
      </integer>   
      
      <boolean>
          <name>interiorIsPositive</name>
          <label>Interior Is Positive</label>
          <flag>p</flag>
          <longflag>interiorPositive</longflag>
          <channel>input</channel>
          <description><![CDATA[Set this flag to indicate that the interior \
              of the structure of interest should be assigned positive distance values]]></description>
          <default>false</default>
      </boolean> 
   
  </parameters>
</executable>
