<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<executable>
    <category>Chest Imaging Platform.Toolkit.Utils</category>
    <title>ReadVTKWriteNRRDsK</title>
    <description><![CDATA[This reads a VTK polydata file containing particles data \
and writes a corresponding collection of NRRD files containing array data.]]>
    </description>
    <version>0.0.1</version>
    <documentation-url>https://chestimagingplatform.org/utils</documentation-url>
    <license>Slicer</license>
    <contributor> Applied Chest Imaging Laboratory, Brigham and Women's hospital</contributor>
    <acknowledgements>This work is funded by the National Heart, Lung, And Blood Institute of the National \
Institutes of Health under Award Number R01HL116931. The content is solely the responsibility of the authors \
and does not necessarily represent the official views of the National Institutes of Health.
    </acknowledgements>
    
    <parameters>
        <label>IO</label>
        <description>Input/output parameters</description>
        <file>
            <name>inFileName</name>
            <label>Input FileName Vector</label>
            <channel>input</channel>
            <flag>i</flag>
            <longflag>ip</longflag>
            <description><![CDATA[Input VTK polydata file corresponding to particles data. The contents of this \
file will be writtent to output files with file names corresponding to the polydata array names. Note that scale \
and 3D position information will be packaged together in one file, with the first three coordinates representing \
spatial location and the fourth component representing scale information. This output file will be designated \
as 'pass.nrrd'. This is consistent with how data is packaged by teem's puller program that is the main engine \
for producing particles data.]]></description>
            <default>NA</default>
        </file>
                
         <string>
            <name>prefix</name>
            <label>Prefix for output files</label>
            <channel>output</channel>
            <longflag>prefix</longflag>
            <description><![CDATA[All output NRRD files will have this prefix. The file names will be determined \
from the array names in input VTK polydata file, so a given output file will have the format: prefix + arrayName \
+ .nrrd.]]></description>
            <default>NA</default>
        </string>
      

    </parameters>
</executable>
