<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<executable>
  <category>Chest Imaging Platform.Toolkit.Particles</category>
  <title>FilterFissureParticleData</title>
  <description><![CDATA[This program reads fissure particles and filters them \
based on connected components analysis. Particles are placed in \
the same component provided they are sufficiently close to one \
another and sufficiently define a local sheet (i.e. they are sufficiently orthogonal to the \
vector connecting the two paticle spatial locations). Only \
components that have cardinality greater than or equal to that \
specified by the user will be retained in the output. Furthermore, \
the output particles will have a defined 'unmergedComponents' \
array that indicates the component label assigned to each particle.]]>
  </description>
  <version>0.0.1</version>
  <documentation-url>https://chestimagingplatform.org/particles</documentation-url>
  <license>Slicer</license>
  <contributor> Applied Chest Imaging Laboratory, Brigham and Women's Hospital</contributor>
  <acknowledgements>This work is funded by the National Heart, Lung, And Blood Institute of the National \
Institutes of Health under Award Number R01HL116931. The content is solely the responsibility of the authors \
and does not necessarily represent the official views of the National Institutes of Health.
  </acknowledgements>

  <parameters>
    <label>IO</label>
    <description>Input/output parameters</description>

    <geometry type="model">
      <name>inParticlesFileName</name>
      <label>Input particles file name</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <flag>i</flag>
      <longflag>ifp</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Input particles file name]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </geometry>

    <geometry type="model">
      <name>outParticlesFileName</name>
      <label>Output particles file name</label>
      <channel>output</channel>
      <longflag>ofp</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Output particles file name]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </geometry>
  </parameters>

  <parameters>

    <double>
      <name>distanceThreshold</name>
      <flag>d</flag>
      <longflag>dist</longflag>
      <description>Maximum inter-particle distance. Two particles must be at least this close \
together to be considered for connectivity </description>
      <label>Max allowable distance</label>
      <default>3.0</default>
    </double>

    <double>
      <name>angleThreshold</name>
      <flag>a</flag>
      <longflag>angle</longflag>
      <description>Particle angle threshold (degrees). The vector connecting \
two particles is compared to their respective orientation vectors (indicating the approximate normal \
vector to the local sheet they potentially lie on). If the angle between either of these vectors and \
the connecting vector is less than this threshold, the particles are considered to be disconnected</description>
      <label>Particle angle threshold</label>
      <default>70.0</default>
    </double>

    <integer>
      <name>componentSizeThreshold</name>
      <flag>s</flag>
      <longflag>size</longflag>
      <description>Component size cardinality threshold. Only components with this many particles or more \
will be retained in the output</description>
      <label>Component size threshold</label>
      <default>110</default>
    </integer>

    <integer>
      <name>maxComponentSize</name>
      <flag>m</flag>
      <longflag>maxSize</longflag>
      <description>Maximum component size. No component will be larger than the specified size</description>
      <label>Maximum component size</label>
      <default>4000</default>
    </integer>
    
  </parameters>
</executable>
