<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<executable>
  <category>Chest Imaging Platform.Toolkit.Processing</category>
  <title>ComputeFissureFeatureVectors</title>
  <description><![CDATA[This program generates a collection of feature vectors at point locations \
  indicated by an input polydata file.]]>
  </description>
  <version>0.0.1</version>
  <documentation-url>https://chestimagingplatform.org/processing</documentation-url>
  <license>Slicer</license>
  <contributor> Applied Chest Imaging Laboratory, Brigham and Women's Hospital</contributor>
  <acknowledgements>This work is funded by the National Heart, Lung, And Blood Institute of the National \
    Institutes of Health under Award Number R01HL116931. The content is solely the responsibility of the authors \
    and does not necessarily represent the official views of the National Institutes of Health.
  </acknowledgements>

  <parameters>
    <label>IO</label>
    <description>Input/output parameters</description>
    <image type="label">
      <name>ctFileName</name>
      <label>Input CT file name</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>ct</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Input CT file to be enhanced.]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </image>  

    <image type="label">
      <name>lmFileName</name>
      <label>Input label map file name</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>lm</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Input lung label map file name. This label map will be used to determine whether \
      the feature vectors to compute are in the left or right lung.]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </image>  

    <string>
      <name>vesselParticlesFileName</name>
      <label>Vessel particles file name</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>vp</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Vessel particles to use for the enhancement. Particles are expected to be unfiltered \
      (filtering is done internally for consistency with other data sets).]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </string>  

    <string>
      <name>pointsParticlesFileName</name>
      <label>Points particles file name</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>points</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Particles file indicating at what locations to compute the feature vectors.]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </string>  

    <string>
      <name>rightShapeModelFileName</name>
      <label>Right shape model file name</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>rsm</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Right lung lobe boundaries shape model file name. The mean points of the shape model will \
      be used to create thin plate spline surfaces. These surfaces will be used to compute certain features. A right \
      shape model file OR a left shape model file (but not both) must be specified.]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </string>  

    <string>
      <name>leftShapeModelFileName</name>
      <label>Left shape model file name</label>
      <channel>input</channel>
      <longflag>lsm</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Left lung lobe boundaries shape model file name. The mean points of the shape model will \
      be used to create a thin plate spline surface. This surface will be used to compute certain features. A right \
      shape model file OR a left shape model file (but not both) must be specified.]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </string>  

    <string>
      <name>trueOutFileName</name>
      <label>True fissure feature vector output file name (csv format)</label>
      <channel>output</channel>
      <longflag>outt</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Comma-separated value (csv) file that will contain the true fissure feature vectors \
      for each point location indicated by the input polydata file.]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </string>  

    <string>
      <name>falseOutFileName</name>
      <label>False output feature vector file name (csv format)</label>
      <channel>output</channel>
      <longflag>outf</longflag>
      <description><![CDATA[Comma-separated value (csv) file that will contain the false fissure feature vectors \
      for each point location indicated by the input polydata file.]]></description>
      <default>NA</default>
    </string>  
  </parameters> 
</executable>
